NETFLIX オリジナルシリーズ
〜
BASED ON THE COMIC SERIES
BLAZING TRANSFER STUDENT
（天の声）
炎の転校生とは
Blazing Transfer Students are agents
who infiltrate troubled schools
and stamp out the evil that afflicts them.
問題がある学校に潜入し
悪を断つ…
この説明は
もういいだろう
You don't need this explanation.
Most viewers fast-forward this part
anyway.
どうせ飛ばして見ている
視聴者が
ほとんどのはずだ
And right now...
そして今！
（シゲオカ）みんな いくぞ！
Let's do this, everyone!
（７人）うお〜！
As is befitting the final episode,
the seven Kakerus
（天の声）
７人の駆(かける)たちは
最終回にふさわしく
are facing their greatest crisis ever!
最大の危機を迎えているのだった
俺らは炎の転校生や！
We are the Blazing Transfer Students!
〜
THE ULTIMATE BLAZING TRANSFER STUDENT!!
BAM
（日花里(ひかり)）
校長 このままでは
らちが明きません
Principal! At this rate,
we'll never settle this!
（滝沢(たきざわ)）
いや しかしな
日花里君…
-But, Hikari...
-I know. Haste makes waste.
ええ
急(せ)いては事をし損じる
But, we're out of time!
This is the final episode!
ですが
もう時間がありません
最終回なんです！
PROFILES OF THE KAKERUS
（滝沢）ああ 確かに
You're quite right.
一体 誰が
私たちの探している駆なのか
We really do need to find out which one
is the Kakeru that we're looking for.
決着をつけなくてはな
I'll have to settle this myself.
私の出番ですね
（シゲオカ）あっ 日花里ちゃん
Hikari.
I wonder...
何かな？
why you would want to talk to me alone.
２人っきりで
話したいことあるって
I didn't say it'd be just the two of us.
２人でとは言ってない
What?
ん？
おい〜！
（キリヤマ）残念だがねぇ
-Tough luck.
-Seriously?
（シゲオカ）マジで…
（キリヤマ）ハッハッハ
I see you're all here.
全員そろったわね
JUMP
ハッ！
（７人）うおっ！
LAND
We'll start the final test now.
ただいまより
最終テストを始めます
Test?
（ナカマ）テスト？
It's not difficult.
難しくないわ
You only need to defeat me in a fight.
私と戦って勝てばいいの
日花里ちゃんと戦う？
We have to fight you, Hikari?
ただし もし負けた場合は
However, if you lose,
you must leave Tanebi Academy.
この種火(たねび)学園を去ってもらいます
（７人）
なにっ！
ええっ！
-What?
-Why?
Fight you?
（コタキ）戦う？
勝手なこと
ぬかしてんじゃねえよ！
What a load of crap!
俺はな…
You see...
I will never make a woman cry.
（コタキ）
俺は
もう女を泣かせねえ
（７人）え？
THROW
（日花里）ハッ！
What?
（カミヤマ）ひゃあ！
（コタキ）うあ〜！
JAB
That's 12 jabs a second!
毎秒12発の連続突き
（コタキ）うっ！
PINCH
ああっ！
（フジイ）ああ…
Kotaki!
コーちゃん！
知ってるわ
女とは戦わないんでしょ？
I know you won't fight a woman.
But this is a test.
でも これはテストなのよ
ハマダ君
Hamada,
the rules say you must fight me.
私と戦うのはテストのルールなの
The rules?
（ハマダ）ルール？
今日の日花里ちゃん おかしい
Hikari's gone crazy today.
Then,
しかし それがルールなら…
if the rules say so...
Don't!
（カミヤマ）
やめてよ！ もう やめてよ！
Hold on, Hikari! Calm down for a second!
（キリヤマ）
ちょちょちょ… 日花里殿
１回 落ち着こ
Let's take a break at Komeda, okay?
Their mixed juice is great!
あの… コメダで お茶しよまい
あっ ミックチュジューチュって
知っとる？
National Railway Punch!
国電パンチ！
（７人）うわ〜！
What's going on?
（キリヤマ）なにぃ！
日花里ちゃんが国電パンチを？
Hikari can throw National Railway Punch?
Okay, come at me.
さあ かかってきなさい
Damn it. I didn't want to use this move.
くそっ…
この技だけは使いたくなかった
ナカマ？
Nakama?
Hikari.
日花里ちゃん
ん？
うっ… 何？ この眼鏡
What's with these glasses?
They're so strong. They're making me sick.
度が強すぎて 気持ち悪っ
I've abandoned my four-eyes character.
（ナカマ）
自らの眼鏡キャラをも捨てる
It's a true self-sacrificing move.
まさに捨て身の必殺技…
ナカマメガネＯＦＦ(オフ)
Nakama Glasses...
Off!
まあ 最後やのに
えらい地味な隠し技
That's a pretty dull secret move
to save for the end.
I'll get you back for this!
返り討ちにしてやる
Don't! It's dangerous to wear glasses
that don't suit you!
（ハマダ）
よせ
度が合ってない眼鏡は危険だ！
国電パ…
National Railway Punch!
日花里ちゃん… 日花里ちゃん！
Hikari? Hikari!
（せきばらい）
（シゲオカ）フウ！
Thank goodness.
よかった あ〜 よかった
You're awake.
気が付いてよかったね
I underestimated you.
（日花里）油断してた
勝負は これからよ
-The real battle begins now.
-Hold on!
（シゲオカ）ちょちょちょ…
Why?
なんでなん？
Why are you doing this?
なんでなん？ 日花里ちゃん
I don't want to fight you.
俺 戦いたないねん
I want to protect you.
守りたいねん
Protect me?
（日花里）守る？
I mean...
だって 俺
on my first day here,
when I first saw you, Hikari...
転校初日に 初めて
日花里ちゃんを見たときから…
（日花里）ねえ 君
Hey, you!
You're Kakeru, aren't you?
駆君… だよね？
だあっ かわいい！ ああ！
Dang, you're pretty!
えっ？
一目見た瞬間から ビビってきて
The moment I saw you...
It was magical.
How should I put it?
なんていうか…
It felt like it wasn't our first time
meeting each other.
初めて会ったとは思えない
運命みたいなん感じました
It felt like we were destined.
That's not important.
そんなことより…
It's not?
そんなこと？
We failed to figure it out.
結局 分からなかった
We don't know which one of you is the one.
あなたたちの中の誰なのか
What are you talking about?
何の話？
７人の駆くんたちが
この学園に集められた本当の理由
The real reason...
you seven Kakerus
were brought to this school.
Wasn't it to become
Blazing Transfer Students?
炎の転校生になるため？
（校内放送のチャイム）
I will explain the rest.
（スピーカー:滝沢）
あとは 私の口から説明しよう
Come to the principal's office.
校長室に来なさい
TANEBI ACADEMY
SCUFF
There is a very important reason
why I summoned
（滝沢）
君たち７人を
この学園に呼び寄せたのには
the seven of you to this school.
重大な意味がある
One of you is the person
who will carry out my wishes.
君たちの誰か１人が
私の意志を継ぐ者
That person is the heir to this school.
この学園の後継者であるはずなのだ
-What?
（７人）は？
The heir of this school?
学園の後継者？
To find out who that is,
それが誰かを見極めるため
あなたたちには
転校初日のプロレス大会をはじめ
you were given several missions
to complete
such as Transfer Student Pro Wrestling.
数々のミッションが
与えられていたってわけ
You did very well
as Blazing Transfer Students.
（滝沢）
君たちは炎の転校生として
実に よくやってくれた
However, I was unable to figure out
which one of you is the Kakeru
しかし
誰が 私が探し求めた駆なのかは
that I've been looking for.
ついに分からなかった
The Kakeru that you've been looking for?
探し求めた駆？
I'll give it to you straight.
単刀直入に言おう
To tell you the truth,
実は 君たちの誰か１人が
one of you is my son.
私の息子なのだ
（７人）えっ…
What?
幼い頃 生き別れた 私の息子なのだ
My son was separated from me
while he was still very young.
FLASH
（７人）えええ〜！
はあ？
ちょっと それ
どういうことよ パパ！
What's going on here, Dad?
-What?
-Dad?
（キリヤマ）えっ！
（シゲオカ）パパ？
（カミヤマ）
え〜！ なんか人間になったよ
Hey! He's turned into a human!
（キリヤマ）ええっ！
（シゲオカ）パパ？
Dad?
TANEBI ACADEMY
Who the heck are you?
（門番１）何だ？ お前は
No outsiders allowed!
（門番２）
部外者は立ち入り禁止だ！
I've never heard about that!
聞いてないわよ そんなこと
You only told me you're looking for
an heir to the school!
種火学園の後継者 探すって
言ってただけじゃない！
Obviously, the heir is my son, Kakeru!
後継者 イコール 息子の駆だろうが
はあ？ 何よ そのイコール
No, it's not! That's impossible!
ないない ありえない！
Then, why do you think I gathered
a bunch of boys named Kakeru?
じゃあさ お前は
私が なんで わざわざ
駆って名前の青年を
集めたと思ってんだ？
I'd completely forgotten
my brother's name was Kakeru.
だって そもそも
お兄ちゃんの名前が
駆だってこと自体 忘れてたもん
You're his sister.
お前 妹だろう
I can't help it. He was taken away
when I was just a little baby!
しかたないでしょ
幼い頃に
離ればなれになったきりなんだし
（カミヤマ）
あの えっと… ということは
So, that means Principal and Hikari
are father and daughter, right?
校長と日花里ちゃんって
親子なんですね？
Didn't I tell you?
言ってなかったっけ？
-No, you didn't.
-You never did!
（キリヤマ）初耳ですぅ
（コタキ）聞いてねえよ
Anyway,
それもそうだが
俺たちの中の誰かが
滝沢校長の生き別れの息子？
that means one of us
is Principal Takizawa's long-lost son.
One of these guys...
（日花里）
この中の誰かが 私のお兄ちゃん？
is my brother?
シゲオカ君
-Shigeoka.
-Yes?
はい
Earlier, you said that you felt
we were destined to meet.
さっき 私に“運命 感じた”って
言ってたよね？
（６人）えっ！
-That could mean we're siblings!
-No!
それって もしかして兄妹(きょうだい)の…
ちゃうよ！ 俺 親父(おやじ)おるもん！
I have a dad!
Cut that out!
やめろや 親父おる
親父おるから 絶対
日花里ちゃんと兄妹なわけない
I have a dad. There's no way
we're siblings.
私にも れっきとしたダディがいる
I most certainly have a father as well.
-I do, too.
-My dad's a great carpenter.
俺の親父も 腕のいい大工だ
まあ
血つながってるか分からんけど
He might not be your real father.
てめえ この野郎！
人んちを勝手に複雑に…
God damn you! How dare you
insult my family!
（滝沢）まあ まあ まあ！
-I didn't insult your family!
-Stop!
まあまあ まあまあ
-That's enough!
Everyone has his opinion,
まあ いろんな言い分は分かるが
but Tanebi Academy's superior system
種火学園の優秀なシステムが
私の息子候補として
did choose you seven
as the possible candidates for my son.
君たち７人を選び出したことには
間違いない
ただ 私自身の目で
自分の息子と確信したかったが…
However, I wanted to figure out
who my son was on my own.
（門番１）校長！
Principal!
A man's challenging our school!
道場破り… いや 学園破りです！
学園破り？
-Challenging our school?
-A very peculiar man is demanding to see
（門番２）はい　異常な気配の男が
滝沢校長と日花里さんに
会わせろと
Principal Takizawa and Hikari!
He invaded the ruins
of the underground bunker.
（門番１）
地下の爆薬庫跡に侵入しました！
An enemy at a time like this?
こんなときに敵…
I'll take care of him, Principal!
校長 私が行きます
Wait, Hikari!
待って 日花里ちゃん
俺 言ったやん
Didn't I tell you I'd protect you?
守るって
お兄ちゃん…
-My brother!
-I'm not your brother, damn it!
お兄ちゃんじゃない もう！
Let's go, guys!
行こうぜ みんな！
（６人）おう！
That must be him.
（ハマダ）あいつか
（謎の青年）フッ
あっ うっ…
（せきばらい）
おい あごが弱いぞ
Hey, he has a weak jaw.
It's not just his jaw.
あごだけじゃねえ
全体的に弱そうじゃねえか
He looks weak all over.
うん…
あちきらでも勝てそうだがや
-Even I could beat him.
-No. Overconfidence can be dangerous.
（ナカマ）いや
油断は禁物や
You all...
お前たち
have come to test my strength,
haven't you?
俺の力を試しにきたんだろう？
フッ いいだろう
Fine.
I'll fight you.
相手になってやる
I have...
俺は
come to this school to prove
俺の圧倒的なパワーを証明するため
今日 この学園に現れたのだからな
my overwhelming power to you all.
So, you're an enemy of Tanebi Academy.
やはり 種火学園の敵か
I will protect Hikari at all costs.
日花里ちゃんは俺が絶対守る
Kakeru...
駆君…
No matter who the enemy is,
my son would definitely defeat him.
どんな敵であろうと
私の息子なら 必ず勝てるはずだ
ここは俺がいく
-I'll take care of this!
-Kotaki?
コタキ君？
I'm sorry, everyone.
悪(わり)ぃな みんな
But I'm Principal's long-lost son.
俺が校長の生き別れの息子だ
（キリヤマ）え〜！
（シゲオカ）なに？
-What?
-Since I was a kid,
（コタキ）
ガキの頃 親に よく言われたぜ
my parents often told me,
"We found you under a bridge."
お前は
橋の下から拾ってきた子供だってな
あっ！
My parents said the same thing
when they scolded me!
そういえば 俺も叱られたときに
よく そう言われた
じゃあ 俺も…
-Then, I am...
-No!
違う！
わたくしこそ生き別れの息子だ
-I am his long-lost son!
-Really?
（コタキ）ああ？
My father is bald,
so he can't be my father!
ダディは…
わたくしの父は はげている
恐らく実の父親じゃないんだ
そう思いたい！
That's what I believe!
Then, I'm the long-lost son too!
（キリヤマ）
ほんだら あちきも
生き別れの息子だぎゃ！
I'm not Hikari's brother!
俺は
日花里ちゃんのお兄ちゃんやない
いや 君だけテイストちゃうから
You're missing the point.
（せきばらい）
Let's forget about that for now.
とりあえず
誰が息子かは置いといて！
Right. We all need to fight now.
ああ ここは みんなで戦うぞ
（キリヤマ）おう！
If we find your brother, Kakeru,
お前の兄 駆を見つけることは
we can also find your mother.
お前の母を探すことでもある
えっ… ママを？
What? Mom?
Yes.
ああ
While you were still little,
まだ お前が幼い頃
my wife, Yukari,
ran away with my son, Kakeru.
妻の友花里(ゆかり)は
長男の駆と共に姿を消し…
（携帯電話の着信音）
（日花里）あっ
-It's a text from Mom.
-What?
ママからメールだ
なにっ？
Yukari Takizawa: Hi! Your brother
is going there to see you today!
You're all coming for me?
全員で来るか
Fine, I'll take you on.
いいだろう！
（７人）ハッ…
What?
Leader?
リ… リーダー？
ああ
I recognize that charisma
and an air of dignity around him.
あの熟練した職人のような貫禄は
どう見ても…
いや 東京湾や島ならともかく
I can understand seeing him in Tokyo Bay
or on an island, but not here!
こ… こんなとこ おらんて
ああ 確か反射炉を作って
国家転覆をたくらんでるとか
Isn't he building a furnace
and planning to overthrow the government?
Okay, let's all go and check.
よし 全員で確認しに行こまい
（６人）えっ？
-Really?
-Come on!
（７人）うおおっ…
いや そもそも…
You're too old to be wearing
a high-school uniform!
もう
学ランを着れる歳(とし)じゃねえよ！
That's right!
（カミヤマ）
そうだよ
長老って呼ばれてるんだよ？
People call you "Old Man"!
But if you're an idol, you can wear
a school uniform
だが アイドルなら
老けていても 学生服を
着ていいというルールがある！
even if you look old.
That's what the rules say.
I shall touch him!
あちき 触ってみるでござる
うお〜！ かっこいい…
He's so cool.
ああ… ありがたや〜！
Thank you!
-Thank you so much!
-This has been an honor!
（７人）
ありがたや ありがたや…
ありがとうございます！
-Thank you!
Thank you so much!
（キリヤマ）
よし 行こまい 行こまい
Okay, let's go.
（カミヤマ）失礼します
-Excuse us.
-That was great!
（７人）うおお…
（興奮気味の笑い声）
-So, what do you think?
-He is Leader.
で どうやった？
あれはリーダーだぎゃ
しかし なぜ俺たちのドラマに？
But what's he doing in our drama?
Damn it! He's making a cameo
in our last episode
くそっ… 最終回だけチラッと出て
to steal the spotlight.
おいしいところ
かっさらっていく気かよ！
僕たちが かなうはずないのに
-We're no match for him.
-Right, not in our current position.
なっ 立場的にもな
でも これは わたくしたちのドラマ
But this is our drama, so we cannot lose!
だから負けるはずがない！
そうや 主人公は俺たちやし
Right. We're the lead characters.
It's possible that he's here
to back us up.
僕たちに花を持たせに来てくれた
可能性もある
Okay...
さあ…
どんとこい！
Come at me!
（シゲオカ）みんな いくぞ！
Let's do this, everyone!
（７人）うお〜！
We are the Blazing Transfer Students!
俺らは炎の転校生や！
Seven of us together
make it seven times more powerful!
（７人）７人全員７倍の…
国電パ〜ンチ！
-National Railway Punch!
Their lethal move,
which hasn't been used much,
（天の声）
ここで 意外と使われなかった
必殺技 国電パンチが
National Railway Punch,
has been launched
with seven times the power!
７倍の威力で放たれた！
（謎の青年）フンッ！
（７人）うわっ！
（謎の青年）ハッ！
（シゲオカ）なにっ！
What?
National Railway?
国電か…
古い
That's lame.
（７人）
は？
えっ…
Iron Arm...
鉄腕…
ダ〜ッシュ！
Dash!
（７人）ぐああ〜！
フッ…
What? I see Mom all the time.
（日花里）え？
っていうか 私
ママと普通に会ってるけど
I told you that she and I went shopping
at Gotemba Outlets the other day.
この前も 御殿場(ごてんば)のアウトレットで
一緒に買い物したって
話したじゃない
You never told me that!
（滝沢）聞いてないぞ そんなこと
Yes, I did!
言ったよ！
No, you didn't.
絶対 聞いてない
パパって いっつもそう
You're always like this, Dad.
You never listen to other people.
人の話 全然聞いてないんだから！
あっ…
Come to think of it, my brother?
そういえば お兄ちゃんって？
P.S. I've sent a photo.
He's grown big and strong!
（７人）
ううっ！
ゲホッ ゲホッ…
He kicked our butts
with just a single punch.
一撃で これほどのダメージ…
Damn it!
ちくしょう
It looks like he'll defeat us.
やっぱり負けちまうのかよ
（シゲオカ）
いや 俺は最後まで諦めない
I won't give up! I'll fight until the end
for the woman I love!
愛する人のために
最後まで戦ってみせる！
（日花里）
お兄ちゃん もうやめて！
Stop, my brother!
Cut it out, Hikari! I'm not your brother!
（シゲオカ）
止めんといてくれ 日花里ちゃん
俺 お兄ちゃんやない
My brother!
お兄ちゃん！
（シゲオカ）え？
あっ… ハハハ！
ああ！ 日花里か
Hikari!
You've really grown!
大きくなったな〜！
My brother, Kakeru!
駆お兄ちゃん！
（７人）駆お兄ちゃん？
-"My brother, Kakeru"?
-You look like you've gone through a lot.
-Hikari!
随分と苦労したようだな
Dad!
父さん…
It's been so long!
（謎の青年）お久しぶりです！
（滝沢）ハハハハ！
To become the most powerful
Blazing Transfer Student ever,
最強の炎の転校生となるために
今まで ずっと
無人島で修行していました
I've been training on a deserted island.
ああ そうか そうか！
-Is that so?
-What an emotional reunion!
感動の再会ね
All you viewers,
as well as the seven Kakerus,
（天の声）
この展開は
視聴者の皆さんにとっても
must have no idea what's going on here.
７人の駆たちにとっても
何のこっちゃなので
So, I'll give a brief history
of the Takizawa family.
ここで滝沢ファミリーの物語を
簡単に紹介しよう
I'm so glad to see you!
It started a few decades ago.
Takizawa told his wife, Yukari,
それは 十数年前
滝沢は妻･友花里に
長男･駆を
無人島で育てるのが夢だと話した
that it was his dream to raise his son
on a deserted island.
そうすれば 最強の炎の転校生を
育てることができるだろうと
He said that was the way to raise
the most powerful
Blazing Transfer Student ever.
You see,
だども
as the principal of Tanebi Academy,
種火学園の校長を務めていた
滝沢にとって
それは 夢のまた夢 夢残照
that was his dream of dreams!
そこで 妻･友花里は
夫の理想をかなえるため
To make that dream come true,
his wife, Yukari,
moved to a deserted island with Kakeru.
駆を連れて無人島へと移住した
そして 滝沢は そのことを
Then Takizawa completely, utterly,
totally, and entirely forgot about it.
すっかり すっぽり
ちちんのプイプイ
ど忘れしてたんだってば！
ああ〜 そうだったのか！
So, that's what happened!
-Yukari did that for me?
-Yes.
友花里が私のために
はい！
無人島におったから
システムじゃ見つからんかったんか
I guess the system couldn't find him
because he was on a deserted island.
（日花里）忘れてるから パパ〜
（滝沢）本当だな
-You're so silly, Dad!
-How could you forget about that?
（謎の青年）ダメですよ 忘れちゃ
（自転車のベル）
Oh, dear! How could you, Takizawa?
（友花里）やっだ〜 滝沢君ってば
You went searching for me and Kakeru?
私と駆のこと探してたんだって？
Yukari!
友花里！
-Mom!
-Mom.
（謎の青年）母さん
（日花里）ママ！
I wondered how it went, so I came too.
気になったから私も来ちゃった
See?
ねえ うちの駆
Didn't Kakeru turn out big and strong?
とっても
たくましく育ったでしょ？
Dad, I will take care of this school
from now on.
父さん これからは
俺が この学園を支えていきます
さすが 私の息子だ
That's my boy!
You truly are the strongest
Blazing Transfer Student ever.
お前こそ最強の炎の転校生だ
はい！
Thank you!
（滝沢）まあ 立ち話も何だ
Well, let's not stand here talking.
ゆっくりと無人島での話
聞かせてもらおうかな〜？
I'd like to hear all about your life
on the deserted island.
Good idea!
（謎の青年）
分かりました 行きましょう！
-Okay.
-Let's go.
（７人）いや ちょっと あの…
-Hey! Wait!
-Excuse me!
（日花里）
久しぶりに家族全員そろったね
-Excuse me!
-We're finally all together!
It was nice meeting you.
お疲れさん
Come on, Kakeru!
（日花里）お兄ちゃん 早く！
（謎の青年）ハハハッ ああ！
（滝沢一家の笑い声）
What a load of crap!
Damn you and your happy family!
ふざけんじゃねえ！
この仲良しまぬけ家族が！
What did you need all of us for?
あちきらは 一体 何だったんだて！
You even made us leave our schools!
わざわざ転校までさせられて…
結局 赤の他人じゃないですか！
You're treating us like total strangers!
よっしゃ！
日花里ちゃんと赤の他人
Yes! I'm not related to Hikari!
いや はしゃぐとこちゃうからね
Why are you excited about that?
よくも わたくしたちを
弄んでくれたな！
How dare you toy with us like this?
（天の声）
つまり ７人の駆たちは
もはや用済みとなり…
It appears that the seven Kakerus
are no longer useful.
（７人）え？
-What?
（天の声）
全員 種火学園を
去ることになっちゃったわけよ！
All of them have been
kicked out of Tanebi Academy!
（７人）えええ〜！
-What?
We've all put something meaningful
to us in here, right?
（ハマダ）
みんな 思い出の品は入れたな？
Today's our last day together, everyone.
おみゃあらとも 今日でお別れか
This was one weird school.
ったく 変な学校だったぜ
みんな
元の学校に戻っても元気でね
-Enjoy yourselves at your old schools.
-Okay.
（ハマダ）おう
（ナカマ）うん
You'll miss me when I'm gone, right?
日花里ちゃん 俺がいなくなったら
さみしいよね？
じゃあ ハマダ君から
You're first, Hamada.
（ハマダ）おう
亀？
A turtle?
僕のカメリオ　大事にしてね
That's my Kamelio. Take good care of him.
He was a gift to you, right?
お前 これ
もらったやつじゃないのか？
うん もらったやつ
Yes, he was.
（笑い声）
え？
（シゲオカ）あかんやろ
That's not cool.
シゲオカ
Shigeoka.
うん
I WILL NEVER MAKE A WOMAN CRY.
（コタキ）いいの引いたな
You got a nice one!
日花里ちゃんのがよかったわ
I'd rather have Hikari's.
Don't make women cry.
（コタキ）女 泣かせんなよ
I'll go next.
次 あちきじゃ
はずれじゃ
A booby prize.
それは わたくしの…
That's one of my frills.
ヒラヒラだ
-I can't use this.
-It's pretty nice.
どこに使うんじゃ
（カミヤマ）結構おしゃれかもよ
Okay, I'll go next.
よし 次 僕やな
Okay.
よいしょ
あっ…
（ハマダ）あっ
（日花里）これ…
-Is that...
-This'll turn you into a zombie.
ゾンビなってまうやん
I don't need it.
俺は使わないからな
I don't need it either.
僕 もっと使わへんよ
-Go ahead. Use it.
-I'll go next.
（キリヤマ）使え 使え
次は わたくしだ
（キリヤマ）おおっ
An exotic banana.
エキゾティックなバナナだ
（キリヤマ）
ハハハッ 食べてくれよ
-Eat it up.
-I'll treasure it.
（フジイ）家宝にしよう
（キリヤマ）おうおう
（日花里）腐っちゃうよ
-It'll rot
-I'll go now.
（コタキ）じゃあ 俺か
よいしょ
あっ
使ってね
Use those.
い… 痛い
-Ouch!
-It already hurts?
（ナカマ）もう痛いのか
（笑い声）
Now, I'll go.
じゃあ 私
何これ
What's this?
変態！
You pervert!
ああ…
（ナカマ）あ〜あ
（キリヤマ）嫌われちゃった
-Sorry.
-She hates you now.
すいません
I'll go last.
じゃあ 最後 僕ね
（ナカマ）おっ！
-Those are mine.
-Glasses!
僕のや
（カミヤマ）眼鏡！
（ナカマ）うん
１回かけてみるね
I'll try them on.
おっ おっ… 何これ！
What's wrong?
-What's with these?
-Feeling smarter?
頭良くなるぞ
No! It's making my vision worse!
いやいや 目が悪くなるよ
（笑い声）
-Thanks!
-No problem.
（カミヤマ）ありがとう
（ナカマ）いえ
Stay healthy, everyone.
みんな 達者でな
-Yes.
-Sure.
（６人）おう
（日花里）うん
Farewell, Tanebi Academy!
（シゲオカ）あばよ 種火学園！
〜
-Bye!
-Adios!
（６人）
さよなら〜！
アディオス！
（キリヤマ）ほいじゃの
Okay, let's go.
（ハマダ）ああ
See you later.
（カミヤマ）じゃあね
-Bye!
（日花里）バイバイ
（カミヤマ）バイバイ
Are we all going in the same direction?
（ナカマ）
あれ？ みんな 同じ方向？
（キリヤマ）まねすんなよ
（ナカマ）してへんわ
-Don't copy me!
-I didn't.
（キリヤマ）
なあ バナナとこれ 変えてくれ
-Hey, trade your banana for this, okay?
-Is this...
（ハマダ）
おい カミヤマ
亀の名前 何だったっけ？
-What's this turtle's name?
-Kamelio.
（カミヤマ）カメリオ！
（ハマダ）カメリオか
You can buy one anywhere!
（キリヤマ）どこにでも売っとるぞ
Bye, Hikari!
（カミヤマ）日花里 バイバイ！
（ナカマ）おらん
-She's gone.
-She sure is fast.
（キリヤマ）
あいつ 帰るの早(はえ)ぇな おい
（シゲオカ）お〜し！
明日に向かって
スタートダッシュ！
It's time to sprint into the future!
Yes! Me too!
（ハマダ）よ〜し 俺もだ！
Me, as well!
（フジイ）わたくしも行く！
-I will too!
-Let's go!
（カミヤマ）僕も行く！
（キリヤマ）行くがや！
Wait for me!
（カミヤマ）ナカマ君 早く！
（ナカマ）待って！
BASED ON THE COMIC SERIES
BLAZING TRANSFER STUDENT
（天の声）
こうして７人の駆たちは
The seven Kakerus left Tanebi Academy.
種火学園を あとにした
そして彼らが出会うことは
They never met again after that.
二度となかった
〜
That was the plan.
But since Takizawa's son, Kakeru,
…はずだったが
滝沢の息子･駆が
returned to the deserted island
that he'd grown to love,
慣れ親しんだ無人島に
帰ってしまったため
these seven boys were called back
再び 彼ら７人が呼び戻されたのは
a mere three days later.
このわずか３日後のことであった！
Subtitle translation by Brian Athey